A Guide to the Fairfax Family Northern Neck Proprietary Papers, 1688-1810
Library of Virginia
Library of Virginia
Fairfax family Northern Neck Proprietary papers, 1688-1810
Library of Virginia
24062
0.8 cubic feet
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
There are no restrictions.
Acquisition Information
Purchased, 29 October 1953.
Biographical/Historical Information
The Northern Neck Land Office controlled 5,282,000 acres in land grants located between the Rappahannock and Potomac rivers, which were give to seven loyal supporters of King Charles II, including Lord Fairfax. Agents of the Northern Neck Proprietary issued the first land grant in 1690. The Proprietary operated until the death of Thomas, Sixth Lord Fairfax, in 1782. For the next thirty years, however, the ownership was in dispute. Fairfax family interest was terminated in 1808, when the last surviving heir sold the title to his remaining manor to a syndicate.
Scope and Content Information
Northern Neck proprietary papers, 1688-1810, of the Fairfax family, including advertisements, accounts, bonds, deeds, grants, leases, legal papers, letters, plats, rent rolls, surveys, and wills.
Consists of: a) rent rolls, 1771-1779, for Culpeper, King George, Prince William, and Stafford Counties, Virginia; b) land grants and surveys, 1688-1780, containing the Northern Neck land grant by James II, King of England, to Thomas, Lord Culpeper and others, and land grants from Margaret, Lady Culpeper, Thomas, Lord Fairfax, Catherine, Lady Fairfax, and Thomas, Lord Fairfax; c) bonds, 1742-1789, for collectors of quit rents of Northern Neck properties; d) deeds and leases, 1707-1786, for Northern Neck properties; e) wills, 23 November 1777 and 4 May 1793, of George Smith of Frederick County and William Allison of Fauquier County; f) plats and surveys, 1741-1793, for lands leased in the Northern Neck, most surveys were made by Elias Poston and George Murray; g) legal papers, including forms, powers of attorney, inquisition, legal opinions, court records, depositions, acknowledgements, arbiters' decisions, notification, agreements, judgments, summonses, and chancery bills; h) letters, 1743-1785, mostly to and from William Fairfax, Thomas, Lord Fairfax, Bryan Fairfax, and Thomas Bryan Martin; and i) miscellaneous items, 1693-1788, including accounts, petitions, reports, memorandums, lists, advertisements, receipts, bills of sale of slaves, plan of the town of Bath (Berkeley Springs, West Virginia), certifications, and statements.
Organization
Organized into the following nine series: A. Rent rolls, 1771-1779; B. Grants, 1688-1780; C. Bonds, 1742-1789; D. Deeds and Leases, 1707-1786; E. Wills, 1777, 1793; F. Plats and Surveys, 1741-1793. G. Legal papers, 1721-1810. H. Letters, 1743-1785. I. Miscellaneous, 1693-1788.
Contents List
- Rent Rolls, 1771-1779, 5 folders (Box-folder Box 1, Folder 1-5)
  - Culpeper County, 1779, 48 p. (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - King George County, 1771, 14 p. (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - King George County, 1771-1772, 15 p. (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Stafford County, 1776, 16 p. (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Prince William County, 1779, 24 p. (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Grants, 1688-1780, 3 folders (Box-folder Box 1, Folder 6-8)
  Arranged alphabetically.
  - Proprietors of the Northern Neck to Charles Broadwater of Stafford County, 151 acres in Stafford County, dated 15 January 1724, 1 p., copy (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Grant of the Northern Neck in Virginia to Lord Culpeper (folded and addressed to the Right Honorable Thomas Lord Fairfax, Baron of Cameron; three signatures of John Carlyle), 27 September 1688, 6 p., printed (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Proprietors of the Northern Neck to John Grymes of Middlesex County, 169 acres in Stafford County, dated 7 December 1730, 1 p., copy (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Proprietors of the Northern Neck to Thomas Bryan Martin, 330 acres in Hampshire County, dated 12 August 1765, 2 p., copy (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Proprietors of the Northern Neck to Edward Mountjoy, 940 acres in Stafford County, dated 10 March 1703/4, 1 p. (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Proprietors of the Northern Neck to Capt. William Pickett of Fauquier County, 420 acres in Fauquier County, dated 4 April 1780, 2 p., copy (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Proprietors of the Northern Neck to James Robertson of Prince William County, 338 acres in Prince William County, dated 20 April 1731, 1 p., copy (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Proprietors of the Northern Neck to John Spry, 117 acres in Stafford County, dated 21 January 1705, 1 p., copy (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Proprietors of the Northern Neck to John Spry of Northumberland County, 278 acres in Stafford County, dated 30 June 1712, 1 p., copy (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Proprietors of the Northern Neck to Capt. John Williams of King George County, 1524 acres in King George County, dated 21 November 1729, 2 p., copy (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Proprietors of the Northern Neck to Robert Wilson of Frederick County, 464 acres in an unstated county, dated 2 January 1755, 2 p., copy (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Proprietors of the Northern Neck to Robert Wilson, Jr., of Frederick County, 400 acres in Frederick County, dated 14 November 1754, 1 p., copy (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Bonds, 1742-1789, 39 folders (Box-folder Box 1, Folder 9-39)
  - Gerald Banks as collector of quitrents in King George County, dated 11 March 1768, 2 p. (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Edward Barry as collector of quitrents in Truro Parish, Prince William County, dated 21 April 1742, 2 p. (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - John Bell as collector of quitrents in Fauquier County, dated 22 March 1764, 2 p. (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - William Black as collector of quitrents in Stafford County, dated 30 November 1747, 1 p., mounted on cloth (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Dukey Swan Edwards as collector of quitrents in the counties of Lancaster and Northumberland, dated 9 February 1762, 2 p. (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Henry Field as collector of quitrents in the counties of Culpeper, Prince William, and Fauquier, dated 8 March 1776, 2 p. (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Henry Field as collector of quitrents in the counties of Culpeper, Prince William, and Fauquier, dated 3 November 1777, 2 p. (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Henry Field, Sr., as collector of quitrents in Culpeper County, dated 21 February 1765, 1 p. (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Henry Funk as collector of quitrents in Shenandoah County, dated 20 May 1780, 2 p. (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Henry Funk as collector of quitrents in Shenandoah County, dated 12 November 1782, 1 p. (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Peter Hansbrough as collector of quitrents in Stafford County, dated 8 April 1775, 2 p. (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - John Hough as collector of quitrents in the counties of Fairfax and Loudoun, dated 1 May 1774, 2 p. (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Angus McDonald as collector of quitrents in Frederick County, dated 12 March 1776, 2 p. (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Angus McDonald as collector of quitrents in Frederick County, dated [3 or 23] January 1778, 2 p. (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Thomas Marshall as collector of quitrents in the counties of Fauquier and Prince William, dated 7 May 1772, 2 p. (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - George Murray as collector of quitrents in the counties of Berkeley, Hampshire, and Hardy, dated 4 April 1789, 1 p. (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - James Newby as collector of quitrents in the counties of Northumberland and Lancaster, dated 8 October 1770, 2 p. (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - James Newby as collector of quitrents, etc., in the counties of Northumberland and Lancaster, dated 22 November 1771, 2 p. (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Alexander Stephen as collector of quitrents in Frederick County, dated 24 September 1767, 2 p. (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Robert Stephen as collector of quitrents in Frederick County, dated 16 October 1769, 2 p. (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Robert Stephen as collector of quitrents in the counties of Frederick, Berkeley, and Hampshire, dated 24 November 1774, 2 p. (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Robert Stephen as collector of quitrents in the counties of Berkeley and Hampshire, dated 13 November 1775, 2 p. (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Robert Stephen as collector of quitrents in the counties of Berkeley and Hampshire, dated 4 January 1777, 2 p. (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Robert Stephen as collector of quitrents in the counties of Berkeley and Hampshire, dated 25 January 1779, 2 p. (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Robert Stephen as collector of quitrents in the counties of Berkeley and Hampshire, dated 14 November 1781, 1 p. (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - Lewis Stephens as collector of quitrents in the counties of Frederick and Hampshire, dated 7 January 1757, 2 p. (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - Lewis Stephens as collector of quitrents in the counties of Frederick and Hampshire, dated 7 March 1758, 2 p. (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - Lewis Stephens as collector of quitrents in Frederick County, dated 6 June 1750, 2 p. (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - Foushee Tebbs as collector of quitrents in Prince William County, dated 9 March 1763, 2 p. (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - Samuel Williams as collector of quitrents in Richmond County, dated 30 October 1765, 2 p. (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - John Sherman Woodcock as collector of quitrents in Frederick County, dated 6 July 1780, 2 p. (Box 1, Folder 39)
- Deeds and Leases, 1707-1786, 10 folders (Box-folder Box 1, Folder 40-49)
  - Lease for three lives. Landon Carter of Richmond County, to Joseph Wilkinson, Samuel Wilkinson, his son, and Massey Wilkinson, his daughter, of Frederick County, dated 27 November 1749 and recorded Frederick County, 13 February 1749/50, 7 p. (Box 1, Folder 40)
  - Denny Fairfax to Elisa Aduddell, dated 15 February 1786 (no recordation shown; includes various endorsements), 4 p. (Box 1, Folder 41)
  - Thomas Lord Fairfax to John Lewis, Lyonel Lyde, and Andrew Lewis, 392 acres in King George County, 27 May 1729, 1 sheet, on large parchment (Box 1, Folder 42)
  - Lease for three lives. Philip Martin, Island of Newfoundland, to John Hartley, Hannah Hartley, his wife, and Ruth Wilson, his grandaughter, of Hampshire County, dated 8 August 1769 and recorded Hampshire County, 8 August 1769. With endorsement, 10 February 1785, 4 p., original (Box 1, Folder 43)
  - Lease. Thomas Bryan Martin of Greenway Court, to Thomas Lord Fairfax, Baron of Cameron, for a lot in Winchester, dated 6 February 1764 and recorded, Frederick County, 7 February 1764, 3 p. (Box 1, Folder 44)
  - Release. Thomas Bryan Martin of Greenway Court, to Thomas Lord Fairfax, Baron of Cameron, for a lot in Winchester, dated 7 February 1764, 2 p., incomplete (Box 1, Folder 44)
  - Thomas Bryan Martin to George Williams, dated 20 April 1772 (no recordation shown and county not specified), 2 p., original (Box 1, Folder 45)
  - Benjamin Sebastian, Fairfax County, to Thomas Lord Fairfax, Frederick County, for land in Frederick County, dated 19 February 1760 (no recordation shown), 3 p. (Box 1, Folder 46)
  - John Spencer, Westmoreland County, to John Bushrod, Westmoreland County, dated 13 January 1707 and recorded Westmoreland County, 5 February 1707 (recorded in Westmoreland Deeds & Wills No. 4, 1707-1709, p. 66-69), 4 p., copy (Box 1, Folder 47)
  - Lawrence Stevens, Frederick County, to Thomas Lord Fairfax, dated 1 September 1766 and recorded Frederick County, 3 September 1766, 4 p., original (Box 1, Folder 48)
  - Thomas Lemon, merchant, Winchester, Frederick County, to John Glassford & Co., Merchants, Glasgow, dated 9 April 1760 and recorded Frederick County, 4 November 1760. With endorsement Ja. Keith, 14 May 1768, 3 p., copy (Box 1, Folder 49)
- Wills, 1777, 1793, 2 folders (Box-folder Box 2, Folder 50-51)
  - William Allason, Fauquier County, dated 4 May 1793 and probated, 28 April 1800, 3 p., copy (Box 2, Folder 50)
  - George Smith, Frederick County, dated 23 November 1777 (no probate shown), 1 p., copy (Box 2, Folder 51)
- Plats and Surveys, 1741-1793, 8 folders (Folder Box 1, Folder 6 and Box 2, Folder 52-57A)
  Organized into the following two subseries: 1. Plats and surveys made by Elias Poston; 2. Plats and surveys made by George Murray and John Mauzy.
  - Plats and surveys made by Elias Poston, 7 folders (Folder Box 1, Folder 6 and Box 2, Folder 52-57)
    - For Christopher Armontrout, 20 acres in South Branch Manor, made by Elias Poston, 25 April 1778, 1 p. (Box 2, Folder 52)
    - Ball's Plot. Jesse Ball, n.d., 1 p. (Box 2, Folder 53)
    - Anne Bucklehill's lot in [Leeds Manor] by George Bell, 19 April 1792, 1 p. (Box 2, Folder 54)
    - Burges' Plat. Jesse Ball, n.d., 1 p. (Box 2, Folder 55)
    - Plats: (1) Showing how Mr. Burgess' No Cobler tract and Maj. James Ball's Mountain tract interfere; (2) What land the Brent town survey took from Mr. Burgess' Kettlerun tract. John Warner, n.d. (Box 2, Folder 56)
    - For Robert Clark, 16 acres in South Branch Manor, made by Elias Poston, 20 April 1778, 1 p. (Box 2, Folder 52)
    - For Robert Cunningham, 254 acres in South Branch Manor, made by Elias Poston, 23 April 1778, 2 p. (Box 2, Folder 52)
    - Mr. John D. Fergason's lots in Leeds Manor, Frederick County, by George Bell, 30 March 1793, 1 p. (Box 2, Folder 57)
    - For Mathew Gilmore, 155 acres in South Branch Manor, made by Elias Poston, 6 May 1778, 1 p. (Box 2, Folder 52)
    - Capt. John Greenfield, 175 acres in Hampshire County, by John Moffett, 17 May 1763, 1 p., copy (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - For Daniel Hale, 88 acres in South Branch Manor, made by Elias Poston, 30 April 1778, 1 p. (Box 2, Folder 52)
    - For Henry Hamilton, 106 acres in Hampshire County, made by Elias Poston, 27 May 1778, 1 p. (Box 2, Folder 52)
    - For Capt. John Harness, 12 1/2 acres in Hampshire County, made by Elias Poston, 3 June 1778, 1 p. (Box 2, Folder 52)
    - For Michael Hawn, 120 acres in South Branch Manor, made by Elias Poston, 24 April 1778, 1 p. (Box 2, Folder 52)
    - For Col. Abram Hite, 128 acres in South Branch Manor, made by Elias Poston, 11 May 1778; For Col. Abram Hite, 71 acres in South Branch Manor, made by Elias Poston, 11 May 1778>, 1 p. (Box 2, Folder 52)
    - For Christopher Huffman, 6 acres in South Branch Manor, made by Elias Poston, 5 May 1778, 1 p. (Box 2, Folder 52)
    - For Alexander [Legeat?], 32 acres in South Branch Manor, made by Elias Poston, 22 April 1778, 1 p. (Box 2, Folder 52)
    - For John Francis and George Leggeat, 181 acres in South Branch Manor, made by Elias Poston, 22 April 1778, 1 p. (Box 2, Folder 52)
    - For Job Little, 60 acres in South Branch Manor, made by Elias Poston, 30 April 1778, 1 p. (Box 2, Folder 52)
    - For Robert Maxwell, 18 acres in South Branch Manor, made by Elias Poston, 20 April 1778, 1 p. (Box 2, Folder 52)
    - For William Norman, 119 acres in South Branch Manor, made by Elias Poston, 5 May 1778, 1 p. (Box 2, Folder 52)
    - For Thomas Parsons, 22 acres in South Branch Manor, made by Elias Poston, 21 April 1778, 1 p. (Box 2, Folder 52)
    - John Ralls, 1390 acres, Stafford and Prince William Counties, made by John Warner, 5 October 1741, 3 p. (Box 2, Folder 56)
    - For William Rennick, 188 acres in Hampshire County, made by Elias Poston, 4 June 1778, 1 p. (Box 2, Folder 52)
    - For Benjamin Robinson, 49 acres in South Branch Manor, made by Elias Poston, 30 April 1778, p. (Box 2, Folder 52)
    - For John Robinson, 48 acres in Hampshire County, made by Elias Poston, 30 May 1778, 1 p. (Box 2, Folder 52)
    - For John Russell of Dunmore County, 313 acres in Dunmore County, made by William Hough for John Hough, 17 November 1775, 1 p., copy (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - For Benjamin Scott, 35 acres in South Branch Manor, made by Elias Poston, 4 May 1778, 1 p. (Box 2, Folder 52)
    - For Phillip Swank, 18 acres in South Branch Manor, made by Elias Poston, 24 April 1778, 1 p. (Box 2, Folder 52)
    - For Laurence Shuck, 46 acres in South Branch Manor, made by Elias Poston, 5 May 1778, 1 p. (Box 2, Folder 52)
    - For Diskin Tibbs of Shenandoah County, 294 acres in Shenandoah County, made by Amos Hough for John Hough, 2 December 1778, 1 p., copy (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - For Cornelius Ward, 20 1/2 acres in South Branch Manor, made by Elias Poston, 20 April 1778, 1 p. (Box 2, Folder 52)
    - For George Weedman, 90 acres in Hampshire County, made by Elias Poston, 30 May 1778, 1 p. (Box 2, Folder 52)
    - For Jesse Welton, 19 acres in Hampshire County, made by Elias Poston, 30 May 1778, 1 p. (Box 2, Folder 52)
    - For Capt. Job Welton, 172 acres in South Branch Manor, made by Elias Poston, 27 April 1778, 1 p. (Box 2, Folder 52)
    - For George Whitman, 55 acres in South Branch Manor, made by Elias Poston, 30 April 1778, 1 p. (Box 2, Folder 52)
    - For Capt. John Willson, 258 acres in South Branch Manor, made by Elias Poston, 23 April 1778, 1 p. (Box 2, Folder 52)
    - For John Wood, 9 acres in South Branch Manor, made by Elias Poston, 30 April 1778, 1 p. (Box 2, Folder 52)
  - Plats and surveys made by George Murray and John Mauzy, 1 folder (Box 2, Folder 57A)
    Arranged chronologically.
    - 300 acres in Frederick County, made by George Murray; leased to Henry Catlett, Miriam, his wife, and Calmes, his son, 23 June 1787, 1 p. (Box 2, Folder 57A)
    - 100 acres in Frederick County, made by George Murray; leased to James Catlett, 18 June 1719, 1 p. (Box 2, Folder 57A)
    - Lot no. 39 and 93, 429 acres, Frederick County, made by George Murray, dated 2 April 1791; leased to John Hancock, 2 April 1791, 1 p. (Box 2, Folder 57A)
    - 202 acres in Fauquier County, made by George Murray, 12 April 1787; leased for the lives of Nathaniel Grigsby, Fielding Etchison and Lewis Grigsby, 21 April 1787, 1 p. (Box 2, Folder 57A)
    - 306 acres in Fauquier County, made by George Murray, 12 April 1787; leased for the lives of Baylis Grigsby, Charles Etchison, and Lewis Grigsby, 28 April 1787, 1 p. (Box 2, Folder 57A)
    - 216 acres in Fauquier County, made by George Murray, 13 April 1787; leased for three lives to John Ashby and others, 28 April 1787, 1 p. (Box 2, Folder 57A)
    - 203 acres in Fauquier County, made by George Murray, 13 April 1787; leased for the lives of Lewis Grigsby, Baylis Grigsby, and Peter Timmons, 28 April 1787, 1 p. (Box 2, Folder 57A)
    - 203 acres in Fauquier County, made by George Murray, 13 April 1787; leased for the lives of Samuel Turner and others, 12 May 1787, 1 p. (Box 2, Folder 57A)
    - 200 acres in Fauquier County, made by George Murray, 14 April 1787; leased for the lives of Daniel Routt and others, 28 April 1787, 1 p. (Box 2, Folder 57A)
    - 205 acres in Fauquier County, made by George Murray, 14 April 1787; leased granted for the lives of Richard Routt and others, 28 April 1787, 1 p. (Box 2, Folder 57A)
    - 200 acres in Fauquier County, made by George Murray, 17 April 1787; leased for three lives to Nathan Beeley, Isaac Beeley, and Izaah Hicks, n.d., 1 p. (Box 2, Folder 57A)
    - 206 acres in Frederick County, made by George Murray, 19 April 1787; leased to Moses Green, 12 May 1787, 1 p. (Box 2, Folder 57A)
    - 295 acres in Frederick County, made by George Murray, 30 April 1787; leased to Joseph Graves, 12 May 1787, 1 p. (Box 2, Folder 57A)
    - 190 acres in Frederick County, made by George Murray, 4 May 1787; leased for the lives of Benjamin [O?]rear, etc., 12 May 1787, 1 p. (Box 2, Folder 57A)
    - 150 acres in Frederick County, made by George Murray, 2 May 1787; leased for the lives of Joseph Graves, etc., 12 May 1787, 1 p. (Box 2, Folder 57A)
    - 200 acres in Fauquier County, made by George Murray, 4 May 1787; leased to Bailey Johnston for the lives of John Johnston, etc., 12 May 1787, 1 p. (Box 2, Folder 57A)
    - 202 acres in Fauquier County, made by George Murray, 4 May 1787; leased to Thomas Smith for the lives of Mary Smith, etc., having been assigned by Bailey Johnston, 3 April 1788, 1 p. (Box 2, Folder 57A)
    - 200 acres in Fauquier County, made by George Murray, 3 May 1787; leased for the lives of Dawson Burgess, etc., 12 May 1787, 1 p. (Box 2, Folder 57A)
    - 402 acres in Fauquier County, made by George Murray, 10 May 1787; leased for the lives of John Keith, etc., 12 May 1787, 1 p. (Box 2, Folder 57A)
    - 200 acres in Fauquier County, made by George Murray, 9 May 1787; leased to James Stigler for three lives, 1 January 1790, 1 p. (Box 2, Folder 57A)
    - 240 acres in Fauquier County, made by George Murray, 9 May 1787; leased to Philip Cooksey for the lives of Leven Cooksey, etc., 12 May 1787, 1 p. (Box 2, Folder 57A)
    - 200 acres in Fauquier County, made by George Murray, 8 May 1787; leased to Joseph Slaughter for the lives of Joseph and Samuel, his sons, and Elijah Ships, 30 June 1787, 1 p. (Box 2, Folder 57A)
    - 200 acres in Fauquier County, made by George Murray, 10 May 1787; leased to Thomas Smith for the lives of Susanna Smith, etc., 12 May 1787, 1 p. (Box 2, Folder 57A)
    - 200 acres in Frederick County, made by George Murray, 29 May 1787; lease given for the lives of Ann Allison, etc., 9 June 1787, 1 p. (Box 2, Folder 57A)
    - 200 acres in Fauquier County, made by George Murray, 28 May 1787; leased to Thomas Smith, etc., 11 August 1787, 1 p. (Box 2, Folder 57A)
    - 200 acres in Fauquier County, made by George Murray, 30 May 1787; leased to Thomas Smith, etc., 11 August 1787, 1 p. (Box 2, Folder 57A)
    - 330 acres in Fauquier and Frederick Counties, made by George Murray, 29 May 1787; leased for the lives of Thomas Massie, etc., 30 June 1787, 1 p. (Box 2, Folder 57A)
    - 200 acres in Fauquier County, made by George Murray, 8 June 1787; leased to Thomas Smith, etc., 11 August 1787, 1 p. (Box 2, Folder 57A)
    - 200 acres in Shenandoah County, made by George Murray, 16 June 1787; leased for the lives of John Kelley, etc., 28 July 1787, 1 p. (Box 2, Folder 57A)
    - 218 acres in Shenandoah County, made by George Murray, 14 June 1787; leased to Thomas Reynolds, etc., 11 August 1787, 1 p. (Box 2, Folder 57A)
    - 256 acres in Shenandoah County, made by George Murray, 14 June 1787; leased for the lives of John Smith, Ann Edmunds, his sister, and Thomas Smith, his son, 23 June 1787, 1 p. (Box 2, Folder 57A)
    - 201 acres in Frederick County, made by George Murray, 14 June 1787; leased for the lives of Humfrey Grubs, Betty, his wife, and Stephen, his son, 23 June 1787, 1 p. (Box 2, Folder 57A)
    - 208 acres in Frederick County, made by George Murray, 26 June 1787; leased to John Dyers for his life and his sons, Isaac and Daniel, 2 May 1789, 1 p. (Box 2, Folder 57A)
    - 200 acres in Frederick County, made by George Murray, 27 June 1787; leased for the lives of Thomas Whiting, etc., 28 July 1787, 1 p. (Box 2, Folder 57A)
    - 200 acres in Shenandoah County, made by George Murray, 25 July 1787; leased to Thomas Reynolds for the lives of Naomi Reynolds, etc., 28 July 1787, 1 p. (Box 2, Folder 57A)
    - 200 acres in Shenandoah County, made by George Murray, 24 July 1787; leased to John Kelly, etc., 1 March 1788, 1 p. (Box 2, Folder 57A)
    - 250 acres in Shenandoah County, made by George Murray, 24 July 1787; leased for the lives of Francis Rolls, etc., 28 July 1787, 1 p. (Box 2, Folder 57A)
    - 273 acres in Shenandoah County, made by George Murray, 25 July 1787; leased to Ezekial Ennis, etc., 11 August 1787, 1 p. (Box 2, Folder 57A)
    - 200 acres in Shenandoah County, made by George Murray, 24 July 1787; leased for the lives of James Owens, etc., 28 July 1787, 1 p. (Box 2, Folder 57A)
    - 200 acres in Shenandoah County, made by George Murray, 27 July 1787; leased to Alexander Macky, etc., 11 August 1787, 1 p. (Box 2, Folder 57A)
    - 160 acres in Shenandoah County, made by George Murray, 1 August 1787; leased to Patrick Quin, etc., 11 August 1787, 1 p. (Box 2, Folder 57A)
    - 160 acres in Shenandoah County, made by George Murray, 4 August 1787; leased to Nicholas Morgan, 11 August 1787, 1 p. (Box 2, Folder 57A)
    - 200 acres in Shenandoah County, made by George Murray, 3 August 1787; leased to William Thomas, etc., 11 August 1787, 1 p. (Box 2, Folder 57A)